Love on the Sidelines is a tv movie, romance,
comedy film directed by Terry Ingram.
A down-on-her-luck young woman who falls into a job as a personal
assistant to a star quarterback sidelined with an injury.
He's never had a female assistant before and she knows nothing about football.
Laurel Welk, played by Emily Kinney.
Danny Holland, played by John Reardon.
Owen Holland, played by Joe Theismann.
Patty, played by Luisa d'Oliveira.
Ava Holland, played by Elise Gatien.
Ron Lucas, played by Victor Zinck, Jr..
Unleashed is a 2016 American romantic comedy film written and directed by Finn Taylor and
starring Kate Micucci, Justin Chatwin, Steve Howey, Sean Astin, and Hana Mae Lee.
The film explores themes of sports, american football,
fashion designer, personal assistant, hallmark.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.